<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>frenchtoast - Tag - Nathan Petersen</title>
        <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/tags/frenchtoast/</link>
        <description>frenchtoast - Tag - Nathan Petersen</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 09:00:00 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nathanpetersen.com/tags/frenchtoast/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Door Country Cherry Stuffed French Toast - White Gull Inn - Fish Creek, WI</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2023/11/06/door-country-cherry-stuffed-french-toast-white-gull-inn-fish-creek-wi/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2023 09:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2023/11/06/door-country-cherry-stuffed-french-toast-white-gull-inn-fish-creek-wi/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Door County cherries top layers of soft browned bread, stuffed with cherry cream cheese and topped with powdered sugar." Door County cherries top layers of soft browned bread, stuffed with cherry cream cheese and topped with powdered sugar.  An absolute required stop during your trip to Door County, WI. Where? The White Gull Inn (whitegullinn.com) is a historic Bed and Breakfast located in the bayside village of Fish Creek, WI.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Sweet and Salty Sandwich - North Street Grille - Boston, MA</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2023/07/05/sweet-and-salty-sandwich-north-street-grille-boston-ma/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 09:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2023/07/05/sweet-and-salty-sandwich-north-street-grille-boston-ma/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Sweet and Salty Sandwich from the North Street Grille in Boston, MA." Sweet and Salty Sandwich from the North Street Grille in Boston, MA.  Simple but perhaps the most satisfying of breakfast dishes. Where? North Street Grille (bestbrunchboston.com), located on the charming downtown streets of Boston, MA, is an inconspicuous establishment which has gained significant popularity with the locals. Opened in 2004, it features brunch delights all day, every day, in a cheerful neighborhood spot.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Vanilla Challah French Toast - La Brioche Bistro - Madison, WI</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2020/07/19/vanilla-challah-french-toast-la-brioche-bistro-madison-wi/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 09:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2020/07/19/vanilla-challah-french-toast-la-brioche-bistro-madison-wi/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Vanilla Challah French Toast from La Brioche Bistro in Madison, WI" Vanilla Challah French Toast from La Brioche Bistro in Madison, WI  Wonderful french toast with a mountain of toppings. Where? La Brioche True Foods (labriochetruefood.com), located off of University Avenue west of downtown Madison, WI, is a classic bistro serving the local people delicious food. It blends exquisite food with a beautiful ambiance for a one-of-a-kind dining experience. According to their website,]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Stuffed Challah French Toast - Sabrina&#39;s Cafe - Philadelphia, PA</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2019/04/27/stuffed-challah-french-toast-sabrinas-cafe-philadelphia-pa/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 17:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2019/04/27/stuffed-challah-french-toast-sabrinas-cafe-philadelphia-pa/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Stuffed challah french toast from Sabrina&rsquo;s Cafe" Stuffed challah french toast from Sabrina&rsquo;s Cafe  Giant stuffed french toast which will satisfy anyone. Where? Sabrina&rsquo;s Cafe (www.sabrinascafe.com), located in the heart of Drexel University&rsquo;s campus in Philadelphia, PA, is a classic brunch spot. With its quaint and cozy environment, everyone feels at home here. Sabrina&rsquo;s Cafe is located across from the Greek houses of Drexel in a old style university building.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Almond Milk French Toast - Monty&#39;s Blue Plate Diner - Madison, WI</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2019/04/17/almond-milk-french-toast-montys-blue-plate-diner-madison-wi/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 20:41:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2019/04/17/almond-milk-french-toast-montys-blue-plate-diner-madison-wi/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Almond Milk French Toast from Monty&rsquo;s Blue Plate Diner" Almond Milk French Toast from Monty&rsquo;s Blue Plate Diner  While simple, this raisin french toast checks all the boxes. Where? Monty&rsquo;s Blue Plate Diner (montysblueplatediner.com), located on the isthmus in Madison, WI, is a retro style diner which dates back to the early 1900s. The ambiance and decorations make for a warm and welcoming vibe &ndash; this diner really transports its hungry guests back in time.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Pecan Streusel French Toast - Short Stack Eatery - Madison, WI</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2019/04/17/pecan-streusel-french-toast-short-stack-eatery-madison-wi/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 19:16:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2019/04/17/pecan-streusel-french-toast-short-stack-eatery-madison-wi/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Pecan Streusel French Toast from Short Stack Eatery in Madison, WI" Pecan Streusel French Toast from Short Stack Eatery in Madison, WI  World class french toast with great flavor and texture. Where? Short Stack Eatery (shortstackeats.com), located in downtown Madison, WI, on historic State Street, is one of the best known brunch spots downtown. This Madison classic is unique in that it is open 24 hours from the end of the work week through the weekend.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Banana Foster French Toast - Bassett Street Brunch Club - Madison, WI</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2019/04/17/banana-foster-french-toast-bassett-street-brunch-club-madison-wi/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 17:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2019/04/17/banana-foster-french-toast-bassett-street-brunch-club-madison-wi/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Banana foster french toast from Bassett Street Brunch Club" Banana foster french toast from Bassett Street Brunch Club  Delicious french toast that can satisfy any sweet tooth. Where? Bassett Street Brunch Club (brunchclubmadison.com), located in downtown Madison, WI, is a popular brunch spot which attracts many college students from UW-Madison. It shares the first floor of the Hampton Inn hotel, just blocks from the iconic State Street shopping and restaurant district.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
