<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Projects - Category - Nathan Petersen</title>
        <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/categories/projects/</link>
        <description>Projects - Category - Nathan Petersen</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 00:00:00 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nathanpetersen.com/categories/projects/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Custom Window Light Sensor: Home Assistant &#43; ESPHome &#43; Adafruit TSL2591</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2022/12/15/custom-window-light-sensor-home-assistant-esphome-adafruit-tsl2591/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2022/12/15/custom-window-light-sensor-home-assistant-esphome-adafruit-tsl2591/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[My custom light sensor installed in its window to read outdoor light levels" My custom light sensor installed in its window to read outdoor light levels  In a few quick evenings, I built a custom light sensor for my smart home to measure outdoor light levels through my window. In this post, I&rsquo;ll explain how I did it. We&rsquo;ll go over the electronic components and wiring, enclosure, software configuration, Home Assistant integration, and a few example plots of the illuminance levels.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>OpenThermo: Customizable Thermostat for Furnace Control</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2020/12/31/openthermo-customizable-thermostat-for-furnace-control/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 15:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2020/12/31/openthermo-customizable-thermostat-for-furnace-control/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Replace the old thermostat in your living space with a new fully customizable version that allows you to tweak the control algorithms used to keep the temperature comfortable.
This article details the design of a custom thermostat device for use in simple on/off furnace systems. It is called &ldquo;OpenThermo&rdquo; since it has been released as an open-source project (see the official GitHub project).
OpenThermo fully assembled circuit board." OpenThermo fully assembled circuit board.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Simulation of Voltage Source Inverter Induction Motor Drive</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2020/05/08/simulation-of-voltage-source-inverter-induction-motor-drive/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 08:52:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2020/05/08/simulation-of-voltage-source-inverter-induction-motor-drive/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Background The induction machine is one of the oldest AC electro-mechanical power conversion devices [1]. In the late 19th century, engineers pioneered the first single-phase induction motor, followed soon by the three-phase variant. Compared with other popular motor types (e.g. DC or synchronous), the induction motor is typically lower cost and has higher reliability. This has pushed the technology to become the dominant player in industrial applications. See Fig. 1a for an example induction motor.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>AMDC REV D Hardware</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2020/04/11/amdc-rev-d-hardware/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2020 14:25:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2020/04/11/amdc-rev-d-hardware/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Advanced Motor Drive Controller, Revision D fully assembled" Advanced Motor Drive Controller, Revision D fully assembled  The fourth hardware design revision (REV D) of the Advanced Motor Drive Controller (AMDC) from the Severson Research Group marks a huge step improvement in quality of design, physical size reduction, and functionality compared to previous designs.
Background About 2.5 years ago, I begin work on the Advanced Motor Drive Controller (AMDC), an open-source project designed for academic research in motor drives.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Optimizing for Workloads: Linux Spinlocks vs Mutexes</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2019/02/17/optimizing-for-workloads-linux-spinlocks-vs-mutexes/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 11:45:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2019/02/17/optimizing-for-workloads-linux-spinlocks-vs-mutexes/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Introduction Operating systems form the backbone of modern processing environments. Millions of lines of code are responsible for enabling programs to easily execute on a given machine. These programs must share the machine&rsquo;s resources, such as processor cores, volatile memory, peripheral devices, and persistent media. Virtualization and resource management is accomplished by the underlying operating system, which ensures the system operates correctly and in an efficient manner. Machine resources should be largely devoted to the user applications which mandates careful system design and implementation.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>CirArrow: Circular Arrow Tool</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2019/01/31/cirarrow-circular-arrow-tool/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 14:18:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2019/01/31/cirarrow-circular-arrow-tool/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[img.diagram {width: 30em;height: auto;}canvas {border: 1px solid #000;max-width: 100%;margin: 1em auto;display: block;}Use this tool to calculate shape end-points when modeling circular arrows using CAD software. The output of this tool is a simple set of points which define the requested parametrized circular arrows. Therefore, this tool should be useful for nearly every CAD program that supports elementary objects and shapes, such as lines and polygons.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Gradled Mini: Prototype Modular Discrete LED Display</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2018/11/11/gradled-mini-prototype-modular-discrete-led-display/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 11:11:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2018/11/11/gradled-mini-prototype-modular-discrete-led-display/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Gradled Mini after design, manufacturing, and assembly" Gradled Mini after design, manufacturing, and assembly  Background This project came into being during my senior year of college at UW-Madison as a personal side venture. In May 2019, I complete my undergraduate schooling. It is not uncommon for students to decorate their graduation &ldquo;hats&rdquo; to personalize them and make them stand out in the crowd of graduates during the commencement ceremony. Typically, people create artwork related to the university they attended (i.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>AMDC: Advanced Motor Drive Controller</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2018/09/05/amdc-advanced-motor-drive-controller/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 09:45:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2018/09/05/amdc-advanced-motor-drive-controller/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Background My involvement in this project, the Advanced Motor Drive Controller (AMDC), happened because of my undergraduate Independent Study project done at UW-Madison during Spring 2018, advised by Prof. Eric Severson and affiliated with WEMPEC.
How did I get this opportunity? Eric, a relatively new professor, was looking for interested students to work on his projects. My name was recommended to him by other professors, so he reached out to me and I accepted the offer.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Razzler: POV LED Top</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2018/05/15/razzler-pov-led-top/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 15:29:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2018/05/15/razzler-pov-led-top/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Background Razzler: the Persistence of Vision LED Top" Razzler: the Persistence of Vision LED Top  During the summer of 2017, I started working on my first real electronics project. This project marks the first time I have ever seen an electronics project all the way through, from start to finish: initial idea, schematic design, PCB layout, manufacturing, board assembly, testing, device driver development, and full firmware creation.
I love LEDs and interactive toys, so I decided that I wanted to build a top that people could spin to entertain themselves.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>ZMR250 Quadcopter</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2016/06/20/zmr250-quadcopter/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2016 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2016/06/20/zmr250-quadcopter/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Background I got into the R/C hobby at a very young age, mainly with R/C cars. They weren&rsquo;t that nice, since I was so young, but boy were they fun. I remember I got a truck one year for Christmas and immediately started driving (and crashing) it. Since we were having Christmas at my grandparents, they didn&rsquo;t really like me hitting their walls with it, so they hid it from me for a while.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
