<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>firmware - Tag - Nathan Petersen</title>
        <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/tags/firmware/</link>
        <description>firmware - Tag - Nathan Petersen</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:00:00 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nathanpetersen.com/tags/firmware/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Tesla Internship Experience, PhD Student Edition, Summer 2022</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2022/11/29/tesla-internship-experience-phd-student-edition-summer-2022/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2022/11/29/tesla-internship-experience-phd-student-edition-summer-2022/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Me in front of the Tesla HQ in sunny California, USA" Me in front of the Tesla HQ in sunny California, USA  I was an electric motor control summer intern at Tesla&rsquo;s engineering headquarters in Palo Alto, California. It was an awesome adventure! In this article, I describe the key parts of the Tesla internship experience and my thoughts on the whole ordeal.
Disclaimer  These are my opinions only.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>OpenThermo: Customizable Thermostat for Furnace Control</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2020/12/31/openthermo-customizable-thermostat-for-furnace-control/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 15:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2020/12/31/openthermo-customizable-thermostat-for-furnace-control/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Replace the old thermostat in your living space with a new fully customizable version that allows you to tweak the control algorithms used to keep the temperature comfortable.
This article details the design of a custom thermostat device for use in simple on/off furnace systems. It is called &ldquo;OpenThermo&rdquo; since it has been released as an open-source project (see the official GitHub project).
OpenThermo fully assembled circuit board." OpenThermo fully assembled circuit board.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Designing a Firmware Driver for Serially-Addressable LEDs for Xilinx Zynq-7000</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2020/07/17/designing-a-firmware-driver-for-serially-addressable-leds-for-xilinx-zynq-7000/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 15:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2020/07/17/designing-a-firmware-driver-for-serially-addressable-leds-for-xilinx-zynq-7000/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Tutorial covering embedded system layers and firmware design (FPGA + DSP) for driving LEDs.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Gradled Mini: Prototype Modular Discrete LED Display</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2018/11/11/gradled-mini-prototype-modular-discrete-led-display/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 11:11:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2018/11/11/gradled-mini-prototype-modular-discrete-led-display/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Gradled Mini after design, manufacturing, and assembly" Gradled Mini after design, manufacturing, and assembly  Background This project came into being during my senior year of college at UW-Madison as a personal side venture. In May 2019, I complete my undergraduate schooling. It is not uncommon for students to decorate their graduation &ldquo;hats&rdquo; to personalize them and make them stand out in the crowd of graduates during the commencement ceremony. Typically, people create artwork related to the university they attended (i.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Razzler: POV LED Top</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2018/05/15/razzler-pov-led-top/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 15:29:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2018/05/15/razzler-pov-led-top/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Background Razzler: the Persistence of Vision LED Top" Razzler: the Persistence of Vision LED Top  During the summer of 2017, I started working on my first real electronics project. This project marks the first time I have ever seen an electronics project all the way through, from start to finish: initial idea, schematic design, PCB layout, manufacturing, board assembly, testing, device driver development, and full firmware creation.
I love LEDs and interactive toys, so I decided that I wanted to build a top that people could spin to entertain themselves.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>My Experience Interning at Silicon Labs - Summer 2017</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2017/09/02/my-experience-interning-at-silicon-labs-summer-2017/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2017/09/02/my-experience-interning-at-silicon-labs-summer-2017/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Update April 2021  Silicon Labs has sold their I&amp;A Business.
My entire expereince at Silicon Labs, as discussed below, was in the I&amp;A division. Therefore, everything I say below is outdated, since the business/products no longer exist from Silicon Labs. Most links in this article to silabs.com are now invalid, but I will keep them intact for posterity.
   Well, thus concludes my summer at Silicon Labs, and boy was it great.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Bluetooth Controlled LED Display</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2015/07/05/bluetooth-controlled-led-display/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2015 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2015/07/05/bluetooth-controlled-led-display/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Colorful display made from serially addressable LEDs for 4-H project.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
