<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Experiences - Category - Nathan Petersen</title>
        <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/categories/experiences/</link>
        <description>Experiences - Category - Nathan Petersen</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:00:00 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nathanpetersen.com/categories/experiences/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Tesla Internship Experience, PhD Student Edition, Summer 2022</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2022/11/29/tesla-internship-experience-phd-student-edition-summer-2022/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2022/11/29/tesla-internship-experience-phd-student-edition-summer-2022/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Me in front of the Tesla HQ in sunny California, USA" Me in front of the Tesla HQ in sunny California, USA  I was an electric motor control summer intern at Tesla&rsquo;s engineering headquarters in Palo Alto, California. It was an awesome adventure! In this article, I describe the key parts of the Tesla internship experience and my thoughts on the whole ordeal.
Disclaimer  These are my opinions only.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Website Update: Hugo</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2022/05/25/website-update-hugo/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2022/05/25/website-update-hugo/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Welcome back to my blog, now completely overhauled and rewritten using the fabulously fast Hugo static site generator framework!
After a nearly 18 month hiatus from this blog, I finally dusted off the cobwebs. Or, more accurately, I threw away the old dusty blog and resurrected it using modern technologies. This post outlines what I did, why I did it, and what&rsquo;s next.
  Hugo static site generator logo]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Olive Garden Pasta Pass</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2018/12/24/olive-garden-pasta-pass/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 24 Dec 2018 19:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2018/12/24/olive-garden-pasta-pass/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I ate at Olive Garden 25 times in 8 weeks.
You might be wondering: why did I do this, how could I afford it, did I get fat, if I am tired of pasta, or even if I am crazy? Keep reading for the answers as I attempt to explain my experience with the Olive Garden Pasta Pass.
The prized Olive Garden Pasta Pass in its ostentatious box" The prized Olive Garden Pasta Pass in its ostentatious box  Not Sponsored  This post is not sponsored by Olive Garden, although that&rsquo;d be nice.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Interning at Silicon Labs, the Sequel - Summer 2018</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2018/09/09/interning-at-silicon-labs-the-sequel-summer-2018/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 15:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2018/09/09/interning-at-silicon-labs-the-sequel-summer-2018/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Update April 2021  Silicon Labs has sold their I&amp;A Business.
My entire expereince at Silicon Labs, as discussed below, was in the I&amp;A division. Therefore, everything I say below is outdated, since the business/products no longer exist from Silicon Labs. Most links in this article to silabs.com are now invalid, but I will keep them intact for posterity.
   NOTE: Make sure you read this post after reading about my previous internship experience at Silicon Labs.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>4-H Electronics Projects Archive</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2018/04/28/4-h-electronics-projects-archive/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2018 15:09:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2018/04/28/4-h-electronics-projects-archive/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[History Growing up, I was a member of the All-School 4-H Club. While a member, I didn&rsquo;t really appreciate the experience; it seemed like a waste of time but looking back, a few aspects come to mind as helpful.
I took electronics projects for many years, from 2006 through 2011, and learned a lot. Each year, I created a display board to show at the county project exposition. The display board showcased a simple circuit that demonstrated a specific electronics principle.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>My Experience Interning at Silicon Labs - Summer 2017</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2017/09/02/my-experience-interning-at-silicon-labs-summer-2017/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2017/09/02/my-experience-interning-at-silicon-labs-summer-2017/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Update April 2021  Silicon Labs has sold their I&amp;A Business.
My entire expereince at Silicon Labs, as discussed below, was in the I&amp;A division. Therefore, everything I say below is outdated, since the business/products no longer exist from Silicon Labs. Most links in this article to silabs.com are now invalid, but I will keep them intact for posterity.
   Well, thus concludes my summer at Silicon Labs, and boy was it great.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Website Update: Jekyll</title>
    <link>https://nathanpetersen.com/2016/07/26/website-update-jekyll/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Nathan Petersen</author>
    <guid>https://nathanpetersen.com/2016/07/26/website-update-jekyll/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Background I get bored, but I really love learning. This combination leads me to regularly experiment with new technology and tools to see how they stack up with what I am currently using. My personal website, nathanpetersen.com tends to be the guinea pig for such experiments.
When I first obtained the nathanpetersen.com domain, I wasn&rsquo;t sure what I wanted to do with it, so I resisted the temptation to install a CMS (i.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
